#### Contact

mimamitchelle@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/maggiemuriithi (LinkedIn) maggie-muriithi.vercel.app (Personal)

#### Top Skills

PHP

Mobile Application Development Game Development

#### Certifications

Introduction to Game Development C Programming

Ruby

Intro to ChatGPT Course

Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3

# Maggie Muriithi

Full Stack Developer

Malindi, Kilifi County, Kenya

# Summary

A skilled developer with a passion for coding and Marvel, I specialize in React.js, React Native, NodeJS, and Ruby on Rails. I have experience in mobile and frontend development and hold certifications in programming languages like Ruby, React Native, and SQL. Currently, I work as a Mobile Application Developer at LUNA Africa. I also have experience in real estate, where I worked as a Head of Property Consultancy and Business Development and Real Estate Agent. My educational background includes an Associate's degree in Computer Software Engineering and a Certificate in Investment and Financial Analyst. I am a highly motivated individual who strives to deliver high-quality work and exceed client expectations.

# Experience

LUNA Africa

Software Engineer
May 2023 - Present (3 months)

Kigali City, Rwanda

Utilising React Native to develop mobile applications for converting websites into intuitive and responsive mobile experiences.

Collaborating with a team of designers and developers to translate website functionalities into mobile app features.

Implementing features such as navigation, data fetching, and data display to ensure seamless user experiences across different devices.

Conducting thorough testing and debugging to optimize app performance and ensure compatibility with various mobile platforms.

PlayPesa Nigeria Frontend Developer April 2023 - Present (4 months) Remote

Work closely with lead developers to design products and solutions to different user and infrastructure problems.

Communicate design ideas using user flows, process flows, site maps, and wireframes.

Maintain standards compliance.

Integrate software with existing systems.

Document source code and ensure that technical documentation i.e. configuration guides, install guides meet requirements.

Coding, unit testing and debugging applications in various software languages.

# Proximity Point Properties Head of Property Consultancy and Business Development March 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 5 months)

Malindi, Kilifi County, Kenya

### Fanaka Real Estate Real Estate Agent November 2020 - March 2021 (5 months) Ruiru, Kenya

I help my clients purchase properties. Also I advise clients about market conditions, conduct walkthroughs, and provide guidance and assistance through the process of buying properties.

## Pam Golding Properties Kenya Agent Assistant March 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 5 months) Nairobi, Kenya

**Ensuring Customer Satisfaction** 

Preparing Weekly sales reports and Comparative Market Analysis Reach out to customer leads through cold calling

Expedite the resolution of customer problems and complaints to maximize satisfaction

Achieve agreed upon sales targets and outcomes within schedule Coordinate sales effort with team members and other departments Valuation

#### **GIMCO**

Assistant property valuer June 2017 - April 2018 (11 months)

Valuation of property and loose assets

Report writing

Survey the amenities and additions of the property

Conducting feasibility studies

Valuation of machinery

Review local zoning codes.

Compare the property's selling value to other buildings in the area.

Ministry of Lands
Assistant Property Valuer
January 2016 - August 2016 (8 months)

Land development and governance institute Associate Researcher February 2015 - September 2015 (8 months)

Phillipines government funded project Data Entry Clerk June 2015 - August 2015 (3 months)

#### Education

#### Moringa School

Associate's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (November 2022 - March 2023)

#### **KCA University**

Certificate in Investment and Financial Analyst, Financial Planning and Services · (2017 - 2022)

#### University of Nairobi

Bachelor's degree in Real Estate and Property Management, Real Estate · (May 2015 - December 2020)

Regional Center for Mapping and Resource Development Certificate In Geospacial Mapping, Military Signal/Geospatial Intelligence · (2016 - 2016)